folks welcome back this is Matt again
大家欢迎回来这又是马特
and I'm gonna talk a little bit now
我现在要谈一点
about repeated games when players
关于玩家重复游戏
discount the future payoffs and let's
折现未来的收益，让我们
talk about more about that and what that
谈论更多关于那个和那个
means so when we're looking at
意思是当我们看着
discounted repeated games the idea is
打折重复游戏的想法是
we're looking at games where players are
我们正在寻找玩家所在的游戏
playing the same game over and over and
一遍又一遍地玩同一游戏，
over again but instead of looking at the
再来一次，但不要看
limit of the means in terms of some
手段的限制
limit of the average of what the payoffs
收益平均值的极限
are going to be in the distant future
将会在遥远的未来
instead people are looking at valuing
相反，人们正在看价
today versus tomorrow differently so the
今天和明天不同，所以
idea of this kind of repeated games is
这种重复游戏的想法是
the future is uncertain you're often
未来不确定你经常
motivated somewhat by what happens today
受到今天发生的事情的推动
and you trade off today versus the
而您今天与
future so it's not the infinite future
未来，所以这不是无限的未来
that you care about but you say I really
你在乎，但你说我真的
care about today I care about it a
在乎今天，我在乎它
little bit more than tomorrow so maybe
比明天多一点，也许
tomorrow's value is a is say eighty or
明天的价值是80
ninety percent of what today's value is
今天的价值的百分之九十
and that means that the next day is
这意味着第二天是
worth if I take today is worth one
如果我今天服用值得一
tomorrow is worth point nine and X days
明天值得点九天和X天
worth point eight 10.72 etc etc so
值得八点10.72等等等
things are decaying exponentially in
事物在呈指数级衰减
terms of discounting and so the idea
折扣条款等等
here is is if I misbehave today now I
这是如果我今天表现不佳，
have to think about what is it how are
必须考虑这是怎么回事
people going to react to that so if
人们会对此做出反应，所以如果
we're trying to support cooperative
我们正在努力支持合作社
behavior in a prisoner's dilemma I can
我可以在囚徒困境中的行为
behave today or I can cheat and deviate
今天就行，否则我可以作弊和偏离
defect and if I do that I'm gonna get a
缺陷，如果我这样做，我会得到一个
temporary gain and then I'm going to
暂时的收益，然后我要
possibly be punished in the future so
将来可能会受到惩罚，所以
the kinds of questions that are going to
要解决的问题
be important here is will people want to
重要的是人们是否愿意
punish me in the future is it going to
将来要惩罚我
be in their interest
为了他们的利益
how much do I care do I care about it
我在乎我在乎什么
how much my discount do I care a lot
我在乎我有多少折扣
about the future or just a little bit so
关于未来或只是一点点
we're looking at a stage game so again a
我们正在看一个舞台游戏，所以再次
stage game just take a normal form game
舞台游戏只是采取常规形式的游戏
we're gonna play that repeatedly over
我们要反复播放
time and now each player has a discount
时间，现在每个玩家都有折扣
factor so player one has a discount
因素，因此玩家一有折扣
factor and so forth discount factors are
因素等等折扣因素是
going to be taken to be in zero one
将被视为零一
generally we'll take beta I to be
通常我们将Beta I作为
strictly less than one
严格小于一
so that it's more interest if it's equal
这样相等就更有趣
to zero that it means you don't care
零表示您不在乎
about the future at all it's basically
基本上关于未来
just a one stage game so generally the
只是一个阶段的游戏，所以一般来说
interesting case is going to be when
有趣的情况是
players care somewhat about the future
玩家在乎未来
but they care more about today than
但是他们比今天更关心
tomorrow and so forth often in these
明天等等经常在这些
games people look at it at situations
游戏人们看情况
with a common discount factor so
具有共同的折扣因子，因此
everybody has the same discount factor
每个人都有相同的折扣系数
which will make things fairly easy in
这将使事情变得相当容易
some cases and then the idea of
一些情况下，然后
discounting is then the payoff that you
折扣就是你的回报
get from a whole sequence of action so
从整个动作序列中得到
profile of actions a one played in the
一个人在
first period and 80 and the teeth period
第一时期和80和牙齿时期
and so forth what you just do is you sum
依此类推，你只是在做总结
up these payoffs but now you weight them
增加这些收益，但现在您对它们进行加权
by an exponentially decreasing function
通过指数递减函数
which is the discount factor raised to
这是提高到的折扣因子
the power of T so if I care you know I
T的力量所以如果我在乎你知道我
get if this payoff was one every day I'd
如果我每天都会得到一次回报
be getting one today plus 0.9 plus 0.8
今天得到一加0.9加0.8
one plus 0.7 and two right so that's the
一加0.7右二
idea okay so when we look at these games
好主意，所以当我们看这些游戏时
again players can condition their play
玩家可以再次调节自己的比赛
on past history so history a finite
在过去的历史上，所以历史是有限的
history of some length T is just going
长度为T的历史正在过去
to be a list of everything that's
列出所有的东西
happened at every date so here a 1 is
发生在每个日期，所以这里1是
equal to a profile of what every player
等于每个玩家的概况
did in period 1 so when the first time
在期间1做过，所以第一次
we played this game what did everyone do
我们玩了这个游戏每个人都做了什么
and generally 80 is going to be what
通常80将会是
everybody did at time T right so we've
每个人都在时间T做对了，所以我们
got 81 to etienne so these things are
到艾蒂安去了81
vectors and they tell us what everybody
向量，它们告诉我们每个人
did in the first period what everybody
在第一阶段做了什么
did in the second period and so forth
在第二阶段做了，依此类推
and then we can talk about all finite
然后我们可以讨论所有有限
histories so all possible histories that
历史，所以所有可能的历史
could be faced with when I'm playing
我玩的时候可能会面临
this game all the kinds of things I'm
这个游戏我各种各样的东西
going to have to think about what am I
不得不考虑我是什么
going to do if this happens what am I
如果发生这种情况我该怎么办
going to do if that happens so in an
如果发生这种情况该怎么办
infinitely repeated game I've got all
无限重复的游戏，我拥有所有
history's what am I gonna do any
历史就是我要做什么
circumstance so a strategy is a map from
在这种情况下，策略就是从
every possible history into a possibly
每一个可能的历史变成一个可能
mixed strategy over what I can do in a
我可以在某项工作中采取的混合策略
given period face to the given history
给定时期面对给定的历史
so from looking at prisoner's dilemma
所以从看囚徒困境
people can either cooperate or defect in
人们可以合作或缺陷
a given period so if we're thinking
给定的时期，所以如果我们在想
about a history of lengths three one
关于长度三的历史
possibility would be the following
可能性如下
we both cooperated in the first period
我们都在第一阶段合作
maybe player two defected in the second
也许第二个玩家第二
period and then both of them defected in
期，然后他们都叛逃了
the third period so that would be a
第三期，所以将是
possible history and then they could say
可能的历史，然后他们可以说
okay now what are we going to do in in
好吧，现在我们要在里面做什么
the fourth period maybe will that
第四期也许会
bygones be bygones and try and get back
过去，再尝试回来
to cooperation maybe we'll just defect
进行合作，也许我们只会背叛
we're angry at each other who knows okay
我们对彼此都知道的人生气
so a strategy for a fourth period would
所以第四阶段的策略会
be what what you do after you've seen
看完之后就是你要做的
different histories of the first three
前三个不同的历史
periods so sub-game perfection again
期间，子游戏再一次完美
same as usual profile of strategies that
与通常的策略简介相同
are nash in every sub game what is the
在每个子游戏中都是纳什
sub game here sub games are just start
子游戏在这里子游戏才刚刚开始
in some period and talk about what
在某个时期谈论什么
remains so it has to be a Nash
仍然存在，所以它必须是纳什
equilibrium following every possible
遵循所有可能的平衡
history so if you take some history
历史，所以如果你有一些历史
start at that point it has to be Nash
从这一点开始，它必须是纳什
for forever on so strategies now are
永远永远如此，所以现在的策略是
going to be specifications of what we
将成为我们所要规范的
would do in every situation and then
在每种情况下都会做到，然后
we've got nationally history one thing
我们有国家历史一件事
to check and it's important here is
检查，这里很重要
repeatedly playing a nash equilibrium of
反复发挥纳什均衡
the stage game so just find a static
舞台游戏，所以找到一个静态的
Nash equilibrium of whatever game it is
纳什均衡是什么游戏
so for instance defect defected in the
因此，例如缺陷在
prisoner's dilemma just play that
囚徒的困境只是玩那个
forever no matter what's happened in the
永远不管发生了什么事
past it's always going to be sub game
过去永远都是子游戏
perfect so for every possible history
完美，适合所有可能的历史
everybody is going to say that they're
每个人都会说他们
going to play the Nash equilibrium
要发挥纳什均衡
forever on going forward you can check
永远向前，你可以检查
that that's a sub game perfect
那是一个完美的子游戏
equilibrium right that's going to be
平衡权将是
Nash in every possible sub game so check
在所有可能的子游戏中都纳什，因此请检查
if everyone else is doing that I
如果其他人都在做我
wouldn't want to deviate so there's
不想偏离所以有
think a little bit about the logic of
考虑一下逻辑
that because it's there's a lot of
那是因为那里有很多
possible sub games to think about but
可能需要考虑的子游戏，但
you can convince yourself that that's
你可以说服自己那是
true
真正
okay so so solving the repeated
好吧，所以解决重复
prisoner's dilemma let's think about it
囚徒的困境让我们考虑一下
a little bit with the context of
与背景有关
discounting now so let's suppose what we
现在打折，让我们假设我们
want to do is we want to sustain
想做的就是我们要维持
cooperation right so we've got our
合作的权利，所以我们有我们的
standard prisoner's dilemma putting
标准囚徒困境
payoffs here of three three four
这里三三四的收益
cooperating 5-0 from you defecting and
与您合作5-0叛逃
the other person cooperating and one one
合作的另一人和一个
if you both defect so the only Nash
如果你们俩都有缺陷，那么唯一的纳什
equilibrium of the static game is defect
静态博弈的平衡就是缺陷
effect with path one we want to support
要支持的路径一的效果
three three if we can so cooperate as
三三如果我们可以这样合作
long as everyone has in the past and a
只要每个人都过去
defect forever in the future if anyone
如果有人将来永远存在缺陷
deviates so when is this in equilibrium
偏离所以什么时候处于平衡状态
okay so clearly that's not an
好吧，很明显，这不是
equilibrium so if we set beta I equals
平衡，所以如果我们将beta设置为I
zero for both players we can't make this
两个玩家都为零，我们不能做到这一点
work right because I don't care about
工作正常，因为我不在乎
the future nobody cares about the future
未来没有人关心未来
then we'd end up with so many defect
那么我们最终会有很多缺陷
defect in every period being the only
每个时期的缺陷都是唯一的
sub game perfect equilibrium players
子游戏完美平衡玩家
only care about the present they're
只在乎现在的礼物
always just going to myopically defect
总是只是近视缺陷
they don't care about the future so
他们不在乎未来，所以
nothing's going to work so the question
什么都行不通，所以这个问题
here is for which betas can we sustain
这是我们可以维持哪些beta版本
this kind of strategy which is cooperate
这种合作策略
as long as everyone has and if we ever
只要每个人都有，如果我们有的话
if cooperation breaks down and we just
如果合作破裂，我们只是
say forget it we're going to defect
说忘了，我们会背叛
forever after okay let's have a peek so
永远好吧，让我们来看看
if you cooperate and the other player is
如果您合作并且另一位玩家是
cooperating if no one's failed to
合作，如果没有人失败
cooperate in the past what do we get
过去合作我们会得到什么
we get three in perpetuity right so we
我们将永久保留三个，所以我们
get three plus beta times three so take
得到3加beta乘以3，所以
a common discount factor for now beta
Beta的常见折扣系数
squared times three beta cubed in the
平方乘以三个beta
third period and so forth so in
第三期，依此类推
perpetuity if you remember your sum of
如果你还记得你的总和
series that's just the value of that is
系列的价值在于
just three over one minus beta
减去beta仅三分之一
okay what happens if I defect and people
好吧，如果我叛逃，人们会怎样？
were playing this discrim trigger
正在播放此触发信号
strategy well everybody else is
每个人都很好的策略
cooperating the other person is
合作对方是
cooperating in the first period so I'm
在第一阶段合作，所以我
gonna manage to change from cooperate to
将从合作变为
defect I'm gonna get a five in the first
缺陷，我会先得到五个
period but then they're gonna see that
期，但他们会看到
and the next period they react to it
下一个时期他们会对此做出反应
they defect and they say everybody's
他们叛逃，他们说每个人的
going to defect forever after so then in
如此一来，便会永远存在缺陷
opportunity we get a bunch of ones right
机会，我们得到了一堆正确的
so what do we get we get five and then
所以我们得到什么我们得到五个然后
beta times one beta squared and so forth
beta乘以一个beta的平方，依此类推
and if you remember your summer series
如果你还记得你的夏季系列
here this is just beta times a 1 plus a
在这里，这只是beta乘以1加一个
beta is 1 and so forth this is beta
beta是1，依此类推，这是beta
times 1 over 1 minus beta so if I
1乘以1减去beta，所以如果我
deviate what happens is in the first
偏离发生在第一
period I get a gain but then I lose in
期间我有所收获，但后来却输了
the subsequent periods so there's a
随后的时期，所以有一个
trade-off and how big that trade-off is
权衡以及该权衡有多大
depends on the size of the discount
取决于折扣的大小
factor so we've got these two different
因素，所以我们有两个不同
payoffs we can look at the difference
收益，我们可以看看差异
between these if I stay cooperating
在这些之间，如果我保持合作
instead of defecting I'm giving up two
而不是背叛我放弃了两个
today I could I could gain by defecting
今天我可以从叛逃中获益
but then I keep the benefits of
但是我保留了
cooperation in the future so I don't
未来的合作，所以我不会
ruin things and that that means that I'm
毁了东西，这意味着我
getting a bunch of twos extras in the
在中获得一堆的二三
future and so when you look at this the
未来，所以当你看着这个
value of this is beta times 2 over 1
它的值是beta乘以2比1
minus beta minus the 2 and for going
减去beta减去2并继续
today and when do I want to keep
今天，我什么时候想保留
cooperating as long as this is not
只要这不是合作
negative right this becomes negative
消极的权利，这变成消极的
then I'm worse off today by cooperating
那么我今天的合作更糟
it might as well just affect so
它可能也是如此影响
difference is not negative if this thing
如果这件事差异不为负
is such that beta is greater than 1
使得beta大于1
minus beta or basically beta has to be
减去beta或基本上beta必须是
greater than or equal to 1/2 so if you
大于或等于1/2，所以如果您
just go through the algebra of solving
只是经历求解的代数
this inequality
这种不平等
you'll get beta greater than equal to
您将得到的beta大于等于
1/2 so as long as people care about
只要人们在乎就可以1/2
tomorrow at least half as much as today
明天至少是今天的一半
they're going to be willing to cooperate
他们将愿意合作
in this and the repeated prisoner's
在这个和反复犯人的
dilemma with these particular payoffs
这些特殊收益的困境
that we looked at before so when we're
我们之前看过的，所以当我们
looking at this this payoffs this payoff
看着这个回报这个回报
structure here then we've got a
结构，然后我们有一个
situation where beta has to be they if
Beta必须是他们的情况，如果
each beta I is at least 1/2 then they
每个beta我至少是1/2，然后他们
can sustain cooperation in this finitely
可以在有限范围内维持合作
repeated or infinitely repeated
重复或无限重复
prisoner's dilemma okay
囚徒困境好吗
so let's change the numbers a little bit
所以让我们稍微改变一下数字
and see what happens so now let's try
看看会发生什么，所以现在让我们尝试
and make defection a little bit more
使叛变多一点
attractive right so instead of 5 we'll
有吸引力的权利，所以我们将取代5个
make it worth 10 to defect
使它值得10缺陷
so now defection looks really attractive
所以现在叛逃看起来真的很有吸引力
what what has to happen well we can go
发生了什么事我们可以走了
through the same exact calculations we
通过相同的精确计算，我们
just did but we're just going to change
只是做了，但我们只是要改变
the numbers right so we've got the same
数字正确，所以我们有相同的
if cooperating in perpetuity x' worth of
如果永久合作x'的价值
3 over 1 minus beta the only differences
3比1减去beta的唯一区别
we're getting a higher number here and
我们在这里得到更多的数字，
then we're still going back to the
那么我们仍然要回到
defect so there's a little bit more
缺陷，所以还有更多
temptation today and when you do the
今天和当你做的诱惑
differences here you know you'll get the
差异在这里，你知道你会得到
same kind of thing except now instead of
除了现在而不是现在
a minus 2 we've got a minus 7 difference
负2我们有负7差
you're for going 7 units from not
你要从不走7个单位
defecting today so when you go through
今天叛逃，所以当你经历
and solve for that now beta has to be at
并解决现在beta必须在
least 7 nice before players are gonna be
至少要有7位好玩家才能成为
willing to cooperate so you have to care
愿意合作，所以你必须在意
about tomorrow at least is 7 nights as
大约明天至少是7晚
much as today okay and so you can see
就像今天还好，所以您可以看到
the basic logic here right so there's
这里的基本逻辑，所以有
trade-offs of punishments tomorrow
明天的权衡取舍
versus a good payoff today and the the
与今天的丰厚回报相比，
the whether or not something can hold
是否可以容纳东西
together as an equilibrium what's it
一起作为平衡是什么
going to be determined by we have to
将由我们决定
know how big is the future versus the
知道未来与未来有多大
present how tempting is the defection
展示叛逃是多么诱人
versus the current what we're doing in
与我们目前正在做什么
the current period how big is the threat
当前时期威胁有多大
so how bad is it if whatever the thing
所以如果有什么事有多糟
that we're resorting to in the future
将来我们要诉诸的
how bad is that in terms of the
就这个而言，这有多糟糕
trade-off all these things are going to
权衡所有这些事情
matter in terms of holding together
关于团结在一起的问题
cooperation in these kinds of settings
在这种情况下的合作
and that gets back to the discussion we
然后回到我们的讨论中
had a little earlier about say OPEC
早些时候说过欧佩克
right there's a temptation to pump more
对，有吸引更多人的诱惑
oil today how much do you care about the
今天的油你在乎多少
future what's your beta what's the
未来您的Beta是什么
reaction gonna be if I start pumping
如果我开始抽水，反应会是
more oil how are they gonna react to
更多的油，他们将如何反应
that are they going to start pumping
他们将开始抽水
more oil and driving the price down how
更多的石油和压低价格
much is that going to hurt me all those
那会伤害我所有人
things matter and they determine whether
事情很重要，他们确定
an equilibrium can hang together or not
平衡可以挂在一起
ok so basic logic play something with
好的，所以基本逻辑可以发挥作用
relatively high payoffs even if it's not
相对较高的收益，即使不是
an equilibrium of static game you can
您可以平衡静态游戏
sustain it and you sustain it by having
维持它，你通过拥有它来维持它
punishments if anyone deviates you
任何人偏离你的惩罚
resort to something that has lower
诉诸于较低的东西
payoffs for at least that player and the
至少该玩家和
important thing is that it all has to be
重要的是，这一切都必须
credible has to be an equilibrium in the
可信度必须是平衡
sub-game that goes forward in order to
为了前进的子游戏
make that work and
使这项工作和
it has to be that the lower payoffs in
必须是较低的收益
the future are enough to make sure that
未来足以确保
you you know you you deter people from
你你知道你会阻止人们
deviating in the present
现在偏离